

Ahmed Ibrahim

Front-End Developer

a.bruhhim@gmail.com

+249902879718

Khartoum, Sudan

github.com/brvhhim

linkedin.com/in/bruhhim

A highly motivated front-End Developer, with a variety of skills and a diverse experience in different fields including Administration, Social Media Managing and Customer Services. I have good experience in Web Development and Responsive Web Design working with HTML, CSS and JavaScript. I am proficient, reliable, trustworthy and effective at problem solving and multitasking.

Khartoum

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clinic Manager Cure Dental Clinic

08/2019 - 02/2021

Tasks

- Managing and Supervising.
- Oversee meetings.
- Socialmedia Marketing.
- Finance and Budget control.
- Process insurance claims.
- Supply purchases.

Contact: Mahmoud Shamrouk - +249960915481

Receptionist

Cure Dental Clinic

02/2018 - 08/2019

Tasks

- Scheduling appointments and staff meetings.
- Customer service.
- Basic assistant and secretarial duties.

Contact: Mahmoud Shamrouk - +249960915481

Sales Representative

MTN

07/2017 - 10/2017

MTN (Mobile Cash) Campaign

Khartoum

Khartoum

EDUCATION

1 Semester in Information Technology Arab Open University - (AOU Sudan)

09/2017 - 01/2018

2 Years in Chemical Engineering

Neelain University

2014 - 2016

SKILLS

Web Developing

Troubleshooting (Software & Hardware

Socialmedia Marketing

Microsoft Office

Critical Thinking

Problem Solving

Report Writing

Customer Care

Time Management

Multitasking

CERTIFICATES

Code Sudan (01/2022 - Present)

Programming Fundamentals including: C,, Data Structures, Python, SQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

CS50x (11/2021)

Harvard University's introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and programming

FreeCode Camp (04/2021)

Responsive Web Design

HTML Fundamentals Course (09/2017)

JavaScript Fundamental Course (09/2017)

CSS Fundamental Course (09/2017)

PHP Fundamental Course (10/2017)

SQL Fundamental Course (10/2017)

LANGUAGES

English

Arabic

INTERESTS

Computers & Tech

Books

Traveling & Exploring

Arts